Finding Aid for the The Francis Robinson Collection
Special Collections and University Archives
Jean and Alexander Heard Collection
1913-1959
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0003
0.07 Linear Feet
Scope and Content
The bulk of this addendum includes color lithographs, plates and articles relating to the work of Alphonse Mucha (b. 1860 in South Morovia), whose artwork ranged from jewelry, posters, furniture, and household objects. At the forefront of the Art Noveau movement (roughly 1890s — 1920), Mucha rose to prominence in both the art and theatrical world through his association with actress Sarah Bernhardt (1844 — 1923), for whom he designed a series of beautifully illustrated posters to advertise and promote her plays. Additionally, Mucha also designed sets, costumes and personal items for the legendary stage actress.
A second component of this collection consists of prints from Vanity Fair magazine from the "Men of the Day" and "Women of Genius" Series, featuring Bernhardt, Jean De Reszke, and Signor Pietro Mascagni.
- (The File Description)
  - Correspondence (incoming)
    - A - Aherne (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Albanese - Alexander (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Alford - Alva (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Alvary - Anderson, John (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Anderson, Judith (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Anderson, Marian - Appleton (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Aragall - Azuma (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bachrach - Bampton (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Bankhead - Barione (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Barnes - Basile (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Bass - Battista (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Beahm - Bello (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Belmont, August (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Belmont, Eleanor (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Bing, Rudolph (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Bing/Callas (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Bing Memoirs (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Bing Memoirs (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Bing Memoirs (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence (incoming)
    - Billings - Bocher (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Boch - Bozenhard (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Brager - Broiles (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Bronson - Brownlee (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Brownlow - Bythiner (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Cabot - Carey (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Carlson - Casieri (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Cassidy (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Cavalier - Cavanagh (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Celebration (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Cehanovsky - Charleston (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Chelsi - Clurman (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Cochereau - Collier (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (incoming)
    - Colombo - Coulli (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Cornell (Katharine - "Kit") (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Cornell, Douglas - Cox (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Craft - Cross (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Crossley - Cushman (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Dale - Davenport (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Davidson - Depardiev (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - de Segvrola - Dixon (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Dokken - Doulens (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Doumene - Dunn (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (incoming)
    - Eaton - Evans (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Faille - Fielding (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Field (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Finmara - Ford (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Forrestal - Frese (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Friedman - Furcron (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Gaddes - Gallo (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Galloway - Genee (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Gentele - Giannini (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Gibbs (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (incoming)
    - Gigli - Gleaves (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Gobbi - Graff (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Graham - Guy (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Habsbure - Hamilton (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Hamlin - Hayes (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Hayes - Heller (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Helm - Hitzig (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Hobby - Horne (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Horner - Horowitz (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Howard - Innerarity (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (incoming)
    - (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (incoming)
    - Lunt, 1941 - 1962 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Lunt, 1963 - 1977 - Lytell (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Matthew - MacBride (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - McCarthy - McConnell (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - McCormack - McCurdy (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - McDonald - Macy (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Magill - Martin (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Martinelli - Mason (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Massey - Maylan (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Metropolitan Opera House Publications (filed by date) (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Meadows - Milannov (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (incoming)
    - Milhous - Morris (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Morrison - Mytton (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Nash - Owen (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Paderewski - Payne (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Peardon - Peterson (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Petina - Place (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Platter - Pons (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Ponselle - Porter (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Powell - Quinn (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (incoming)
    - Ragland - Raisa (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Record - Robeson (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Robinson - Bossi (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Rothier - Rysanek (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Saher - Scheider (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Schieffelin - Self (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Self - Sharp (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Sheean - Siler (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Sills - Skinner (Cornelia Otis) (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Skinner - Sloan (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (incoming)
    - Slote - Spragens (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Stahlamn - Steber (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Steichen - Stevens (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Stewart - Strobel (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Sullivan - Swift (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Talignani - Templeton (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Terris - Thomas (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Thompson - Toscanini (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (incoming)
    - Toumanova - Tucker (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Tunney - Tyers (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Ugolini - Vaughn (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Veitch - Wallmann (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Walsh - Welitsch (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Wells - Winters (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Wirth - Woods (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Alexander Woollcott (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Work - Zwilich (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (incoming)
    - Bemis - Benson (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Bentley - Bernstein (Herman) (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Leonard Bernstein and Family (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Raisa - Raven (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Composers (1)
    - Amram, David (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Bach (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Barber (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Beethoven (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Bartok (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Bellini (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Berlioz (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Billings, William (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Blitzstein, Marc (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Boito, Arrigo (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Brahms (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Buttern (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Bruckner, Anton (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Chopin (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Copland (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Debussy (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Donizetti (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Dvorak (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Ellington, Duke (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Foster, Stephen (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Friml, Rudolf (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Composers (2)
    - Gershwin (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Gilbert & Sullivan (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Grieg (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Handel (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Handy, W. C. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Berbert, Victor (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Hopkinson, Francis (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Hughes, Patrick C. (Spike) (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Hundley, Richard (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Ives (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Lehar, Franz (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Leoncavallo, Ruggiero (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Liszt (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Mahler (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Wascagni (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Massenet (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Mennin, Peter (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Menotti (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Milhaud (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Mozart (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Mussorgsky (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Parker, Horatio (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Porter, Cole (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Prokofiev (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Puccini (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Composers (3)
    - Rachmaninoff (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Ravel (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Respighi (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Rimsky - Korsakov (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Rorem, Ned (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Rossini (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Scarlatti (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Schubert (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Schumann (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Scriabin, Alexander (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Shostakovich (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Smith, John S. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Smyth, Ethel (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Sousa (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Strauss Family (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Strauss, Richard (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Stravinsky (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Taylor, Deems (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Thomson, Virgil (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Vaughan, Denis (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Verdi (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Composers (4)
    - Verdi (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Wagner (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Wagner (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Walton, William (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Webern, Anton (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Weill, Kurt (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Weissel, George (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Instrumentalists - Pianists (1)
    - Instrumentalists - General (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Pianists - General (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Backhaus, Wilhelm (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Battista, Joseph (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Bauer, Harold (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Bevington, Agnes (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Bolet (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Brailowsky, Alexander (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Browning, John (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Carreno, Teresa (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Carrillo, Ines G. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Cliburn (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Cortot, Alfred (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Deering, Henri (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - De pachmann, Vladimir (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Dubal, David (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Eschenback, Christoph (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Fiore, George (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Francois, Samson (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Frantz, Dalics (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Friedman (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Ganz, Rudolph (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Gieseking, Walter (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Gilels, Emil (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Gorodnitzki, Sascha (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Grainger, Percy (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Mess, Myra (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Hofmann (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Hopekirk, Helen (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Horowitz (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Istomin, Eugene (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Janis, Byron (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Jonas, Maryla (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Joseffy, Rafael (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Joyce, Eileen (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Kape II, William (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Kleiner, Arthur (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Kropp, Myron (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Instrumentalists - Pianists (2)
    - Labunski, Wiktor (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Landowska, Wanda (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Leschetizky, Theodore (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Levant (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Levitzki, Mischa (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Lhevinne, Rosina (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - List, Eugene (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Loessel, Edward (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Mehus, Belle (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Moiseiwitsch, Benno (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Muenz, Mieczyslaw (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Novaes, Gviomar (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Orloff, Nikolai (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Paderewski (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Petri, Egon (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Pugno, Raoul (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Robinson, Frank "Sugar Chile" (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Rosenthal, Moriz (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Sanroma, Jesus M. (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Schnabel, Arthur (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Serkin (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Stoj ouski, Sigi smund (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Turech, Rosolyn (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Von Bulow, Hans (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Waller, Thomas Wright (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Watts (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Wei ssenberg, Sigi (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Zabriskie, John G. (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Duo-Pianists (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Instrumentalists - Pianists (3)
    - Paderewski, Jan Ignace (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Paderewski, Jan Ignace (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Paderewski, Jan Ignace (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Paderewski, Jan Ignace (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Paderewski, Jan Ignace (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Paderewski, Jan Ignace (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Instrumentalists - Violinists
    - Violinists - General (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Auer, Leopold (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Burgin, Richard (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Busch, Adolf (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Carol, Norman (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Gugat (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Davis, David (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Elman, Mischa (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Enesco, Georges (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Friedman, Erick (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Heifetz (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Heifetz (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Kochanski, Paul (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Kreisler (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Instrumentalists - Violinists, Cellists, Organists, etc.
    - Lumia, Guy (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Menuhin (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - IVfilstein, Nathan (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Paganini, Niccolo (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Perlman, Itzhak (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Rabinof, Benno (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Ricci, Ruggiero (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Rudie, Robert (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Rubinoff (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Sarasate, Pablo (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Sorantin, Erich (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Spalding, Albert (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Stern (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Szeryng, Henryk (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Szigeti, Joseph (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Voos, Clara Mathilda (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Zimbalist (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Cellists - Individual (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Casals, Pablo (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - markevitch, Dimitry (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Piatigorsky, Gregor (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - String Quartets (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Guistarist - Segovia (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Organists (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Cambron, Elise (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Biggs, E. Power (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Cochercan, Pierre (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Dickinsm, Clarance (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - John Grady (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Trumpeter - Louis Armstrong (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Mis. Instrumentalists (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Graham Washington Jackson (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Musicians - General (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Boulanger, Nadia (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Samarott, Olga (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Mme. Anna E. Schoen - Rene (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Orchestras (1)
    - Orchestras - General (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Berlin Philharmonic (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Boston Pops (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - American Symphony (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Boston (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Bronx Symphony (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Chicago (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Cincinnati (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Cleveland (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Denver (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Los Angeles (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Orchestras (2)
    - Minneapolis (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Nashville (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - NBC Symphony (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - New Orleans (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - New York Philharmonic (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - New York Philharmonic (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Orchestras (3)
    - New York Philharmonic (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - New York Symphony (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Oakland (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Philadelphia (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Queen's Hall Orchestra (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - St. Louis (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Tulsa Philharmonic (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Vienna Orchestra (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Vienna Philharmonic (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Watergate Symphony (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Wheeling Symphony (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Conductors (1)
    - Conductors - General (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Adler, Kurt (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Alessandro, Victor (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Antek, Samuel (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Bamboschek, Giuseppe (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Beecham, Thomas (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Bohm, Karl (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Boulez, Pierre (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Busch, Fritz (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Sarah Caldwell (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Cantelli, Guido (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Carralho, Eleazer de (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Cimara, Pietro (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Coates, Albert (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Creatore, Giuseppe (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Damrosch, Walter (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Davis, Colin (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Fennell, Frederick (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Furtwaengler, Wilhelm (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Hagen, Walter (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Ivwin Hoffman (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Iturbi, Jose (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Klemperer, Otto (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Kostelanetz, Andre (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Koussevitzky, Serge (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Joset Krips (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Kryl, Bohumir (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Ratael Kubelik (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Conductors (2)
    - Leinsdorf, Erich (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Levine, James (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Maazel, Lorin (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Maretzek, Max (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Mehta, Zubin (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Monteux, Pierre (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Munch, Charles (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Ormandy, Eugene (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Polacco, Giorgio (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Reiner, Fritz (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Rescigno, Nicola (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Rieger, Fritz (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Rodzinski, Artur (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Salmaggi, Alfredo (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - S chippers, Thomas (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Sebastinan, Georges (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Seidl, Anton (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Solti, George (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Steinberg, William (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Stokowski, Leopold (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Stokowski, Leopold (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Stolz, Robert (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Szell, George (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Conductors (3)
    - Von Karajan, Herbert (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Thomas, Michael Tilson (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Thomas, Theodore (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Thomas, Arturo (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Toscanini, Arturo (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Toscanini, Arturo (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Walter, Bruno (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Whiteman, Paul (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Recordings (1)
    - Recording - General (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - American Gramophone Society (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Angel Records (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Association for Record Sound Collections, Inc. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Bauer, Roberto (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - British Institute of Recorded Sound (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Louis Bullaro (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Caedmaon Recordings (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Capricorn (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Cetra - Soria Records (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Collctors' Corner (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Collectors Record Shop (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Columbia (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Connoisseurs' Record Club (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Decca Records (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Deutsche Grammophon (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Disc Trading Post (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Edison (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Eterna (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - The Everest Record Group (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Fabbri & Partners Ltd. (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Famous Records of the Past (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Fillipi, Theodore (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Foldi, Andrew (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Folkways Records (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Fonotipia Records (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Golden Memories Records, Inc. (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Gramophone Shop (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Recordings (2)
    - High Fidelity (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Historic Record Society (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - International Record Collectors' Club (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - International Records Agency (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Kastlemusick, Inc. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Kendiz, David (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Kurtz, Henry F. & Margaret (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - L & M Records (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - London (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Ludus, Tonalis (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Lyrichord (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - MCA Records Ltd. (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - John McCormack Society (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Perry J. Mastrange (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - The Momory Shop (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Merit Record Shop (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Morehouse - Barlow Co. (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Music - Appreciation Records (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - The Music Den (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Musical Heritage Society (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Musicraft (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - National Gramophone Co. (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - The New Records (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - N. Y. Band Instrument Co. (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - N. Y. Gramophone Society (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - N. Y. Public Library (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Nonesuch Records (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Polomino Records (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Parnassus Records (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Period Records (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Personalized Record Service (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - E. F. Prescott (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Recordings (3)
    - RCA Visitors (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - RCA Visitor Records Victor and Bluebird Records, etc. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Recordings (4)
    - Rare Records (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - The Record Album (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Record Collectors Service (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - The Record Hunter (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Record News (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Records Resurrected (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Ross, court & Co. (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Round Sound West (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Saturday Review (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Scala Records (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Schwann Publications (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Marvin Smissman (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - H. Royer Smith Co. (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Stereo Review (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Talking Machine Records (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Roland Teuchtler (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Variety Records (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Veritas Records (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Vocal Record Collectors' Society (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - World - Wide Record & Music Agency (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Music Festivals (1)
    - Music - Festival Information (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Academy of Music, Morthampton, Mass. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Aims Summer Vocal Institute (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Aldeburgh (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - American Institute of Musical Studies (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Aspen Institute of Music (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Bayreuth (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Bayreuth (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Bayreuth (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Bayreuth (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Music Festivals (2)
    - Bayreuth (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Berliner Festwochen, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Blossom Music Festival (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Caramoor (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Central City (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Cincinnati May Festival (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Community Consert (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Eastman (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Edinburgh Festival (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Music Festivals (3)
    - Edinburgh Festival (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Expo 67 World Festival (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Fisk University Festival (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Glundebourne (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Goethe Music Festival (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Guelph Spring Festival (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Harlem School of the Arts (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Hollywood Bowl (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - International Festival of Orchestras (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Juilliard (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Lincoln Center Cultural Seminar (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Lincoln Festival (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - LSU Festival (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Loyola University College of Music (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - MacDowell Colony (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Music. Festivals (4)
    - Maggio Musicak Fioventino (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Manhattan School of Music (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Montreal Festival (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Mozart Fest Wurzburg (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Munich (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Nashville Conservatory of Music (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - New World Contemporary Festival of the Arts (Box 35, Folder 7)